Aw, it's just Iike my grandma
with her parrot.
(Bernadette:)And after she lost her marbles,
with her remote control.
(Sheldon:)My phone's on the desk over there.
Take a picture of us together.
(Sheldon:)Make it good enough to go on a mug,
a mouse pad and a calendar.
(Sheldon:)If you were a dove,
I'd call you Lovey Dovey.
(Sheldon:)Oh, who am I kidding? This isn't a moment
for strict adherence to the literal.
You're just my little Lovey Dovey,
aren't you?
I guess you gotta have hollow bones
to get some sugar around here.
(Bernadette:)I still think
he looks like someone's pet.
(Bernadette:)Maybe we should put up posters.
(Sheldon:)Yes, it should have a big picture of him
and the words:
"ls this your bird? Not anymore."
We're gonna have
so much fun together.
(Sheldon:)You can carry messages
to all my enemies.